RAZIA AKBARI

Kabul 1007 akbariharis14@gmail.com +93(0)789060360

As a medical student and associate degree holder in computer science, I possess a unique combination of skills and knowledge in both healthcare and technology. With professional experience in HR and leadership, I have developed strong communication, organizational, and problem-solving skills that enable me to excel in any role. I am passionate about using my diverse background to make a positive impact on the healthcare and Tech industries.

Work Experience

HR and Digital Marketing Intern

GAO Tek Inc

January 2023 to January 2023

Assisting with recruitment and hiring processes

Maintaining employee records and files

Coordinating employee benefits and compensation

Conducting new hire orientations and onboarding

Assisting with performance management and employee relations issues

Responding to employee inquiries and requests for information

Coordinating training and development programs for employees

Assisting with HR projects and initiatives as needed

Ensuring compliance with HR policies, procedures, and regulations

Providing administrative support to the HR department

HR admin/Liaison Officer

Projectlockdown

January 2020 to December 2021

Assisted Senior HR members with various tasks.

Worked as a reliable and dedicated team member in the HR department, dedicated to fostering the mission of PLD's.

Recorded and reported employee issues, and brought them to Senior HR members when necessary. Reported important events and incidences to senior HR members.

Education

Associate of Science in Computer Science

University of the People - Pasadena, CA November 2021 to Present

Therapeutic Medicine

Ghalib University

Afghan Turk Maarif High school

February 2016 to December 2020

Skills

- Interpretation
- Translation
- Human Resources
- HTML5
- Java
- JavaScript
- Web development
- Canva
- Figma
- Bilingual
- Human Resources Management
- Bootstrap
- CSS
- Python
- Computer Science
- Git
- Digital design
- Graphic design
- Leadership
- Linguist Experience

Languages

- Pashto Expert
- Persian Expert
- English Fluent
- Turkish Intermediate

Links

Reference

Mursal Ayobi - HR Team Leader at GAO Tek Inc. mursalayobi1379@gmail.com

Mr. Samiullah Shirzai | HR Supervisor at GAO Tek Inc

samiullah_sherzai@hotmail.com